https://whistleblower.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Government Accountability Project
Skip to content
(202) 457-0034|info@whistleblower.org
Support Us Donate OnlineHow to Make a Donation of SecuritiesOther Ways to DonatePlanned GivingContact
ABOUT Our StoryOur TeamBoard of DirectorsJoin The TeamAnnual ReportsISSUES Our COVID ResponseCorporate & Financial AccountabilityEnvironment, Energy, & Climate ChangeGovernment AccountabilityInternational Whistleblower RightsNational SecurityPublic HealthWHAT WE DO Education & PartnershipsLegislative InitiativesLitigationInvestigationsNEWS News HitsLettersPress ReleasesBlogPress InquiriesRESOURCES EVENTSDONATETake Action
Search for:
Privacy PolicyWhistle.Blower2019-12-13T07:48:36-05:00
Privacy Policy
This website acknowledges your right to privacy. Moreover, the Government Accountability Project fights everyday to defend this constitutionally-guaranteed right on behalf of all Americans. What follows is a description of the minimal information this site collects about donors and visitors, the security measures used to protect this information, and ways you can contact Government Accountability Project about any privacy-related issues.
Online Donations
All online donations to Government Accountability Project are processed through Salsa Labs using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer technology to encrypt personal information. Salsa Labs does not disclose credit card information and works with partners to provide a secure environment for credit card donations. Salsa Labs will not share your information with any third-party organization without explicit permission.
e-mail
Visitors to the Government Accountability Project website can submit their e-mail address by signing up on the homepage. Government Accountability Project will not rent, sell or share your e-mail address. Government Accountability Project uses this information to keep in touch through e-News and e-Alerts. If you wish to remove your e-mail address from these communications, please use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of e-News and e-Alert messages or e-mail your request to info@whistleblower.org.
Intake Application
All intake applications are confidential. To protect your privacy, Government Accountability Project uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer technology to safeguard data.
Confidential Government Accountability Project Client Names and Witnesses
Any communication by parties seeking to report wrongdoing is made in the strictest confidence. Communication is confidential and any names, content and related issues will not be shared with any party, agency or company without consent. Government Accountability Project has fought and prevailed for this specific right with two legal subpoenas in federal court that would have required revealing names—one in a case involving the Department of Justice and the other against Food Lion, Inc. See United States v. Garde, 673 F. Supp. 604, 606 (D.D.C. 1987), app. dism., 848 F.2d 1037 (D.C. Cir. 1988).
Direct Mail
Government Accountability Project complies with the Rules of Business Ethics and Practices from the Association of Direct Mail Fundraising Council and the Direct Marketing Association Non-profit Council. Information about any members who request that his or her name not be used for exchange or rental purposes. Please contact us at info@whistleblower.org if you wish to remove your mailing address from these uses, request corrections, or have your name removed from our mailing list.
Telephone Calls
From time to time, some Government Accountability Project donors may receive a call from us explaining ways they can join the fight for accountability (e.g. by writing a letter to their representatives) or requesting support. If you wish to be removed from the call list, please call Hudson Bay Member Services at 800-876-2454 or send an e-mail requesting call list removal to info@whistleblower.org.
Refund Policy
If a donation is made in error, Government Accountability Project will refund the donation in-full if the donor makes a request within 60 days of the transaction. To process a refund request, please contact info@whistleblower.org.
NEWSROOM
Letter to NARA on Preservation of Presidential Records
The Guardian: ‘Incredibly dangerous job’: concerns safety is slipping at US meat plants
The Detroit News: Trump rape accuser says slander isn’t a presidential duty
Letter on Further Improving the House Committee on Appropriations
National Review: ‘Falsehood Flies, and Truth Comes Limping After It’
RESOURCESPrivacy PolicyFinancialsResources & PublicationsSign Up for the Latest Whistleblower NewsClick Here to Sign Up
CONTACT Address:
1612 K St. NW, Suite #1100
Washington DC, 20006
To Request Assistance:
Fill out our Intake Form
General Inquires:
(202) 457-0034
info@whistleblower.org
Media Inquires:
AndrewH@whistleblower.org
© Copyright 2020   |   DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT CAUSE INSPIRED MEDIA   |  Government Accountability Project is a 501c3 Organization. EIN# 52-1343924
facebooktwitterlinkedin
Seek Assistance
